Guide to the David Gordon George Papers, 1919-1976 and undated, bulk 1935-1965 RL.00441
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Materials and Writings Series, 1937-1974 and undated, 1 box
  - Where Will Hitler Stop?, undated (Box 9)
- Scrapbooks, Ledgers, and Political Ephemera Series, 1919-1960 and undated, 3 boxes
  Contains membership and financial information in books for the Southern Electoral Reform League and Virginial Commonwealth League as well as a book of clippings and a scrapbook. The scrapbook chronicles the leisure aspects of George's travels to and within Britain. Menus and othe ephemera from the R.M.S. Queen Elizabeth and Queen Mary ocean liners as well as numerous photographs of on-board friends are included, as are numerous photographs of George and his hosts in Brighton, Woking, Bournemouth, and London as well as Scotland. In addition, some photographs document the English countryside and a few show damage incurred in cities during World War II. The scrapbook includes numerous clippings, product packaging, and travel and attraction tickets as well. Political ephemera, mostly pins, includes delegate pins to a several national labor meetings and buttons for political candidates, among them George Wallace.
  - Clippings book, 1919-1927 (Box 9)
  - Receipt book for Virginia Commonwealth League, 1946 May-1950 May (Box 10)
  - Financial ledger for Southern Electoral Reform League, 1940 Mar. 16-1942 Apr. 30 (Box 10)
  - Political Ephemera, 1947-1960 and undated, 3 small boxes (Box 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Box 11)
- Oversize Materials, 1927-1967, 1 box
  Comprises large items from other series. Numerous newspapers and large clippings related to elections and contemporary events, notably German aggression during the leadup to World War II are included. In addition, the bulk of the original copies of George's newspaper articles from the Printed Material and Writings series are housed in Oversize Materials. German language lesson worksheets completed by George via correspondence with the Pelman Institute are included as well.
  - Subject Files
    - British Service Entertainment Committee, 1946 (Box 12)
    - Elections
      - Election statistics, 1933 (Box 12)
      - George campaign, 1941 (Box 12)
      - Plunkett, Moss A. campaign, 1945 (Box 12)
    - Socialist Activities
      - Clippings (Box 12)
      - Germany etc, 1927-1939 and undated, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Personal Files
    - Clippings, 1946 (Box 12)
    - School reunion, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Printed Materials and Writings
    - Newspapers and clippings, 1934-1937, 2 folders (Box 12)